He got the drop on us again...
When are the holy knights
gonna do something about it?
Everyone, run! It's him!
It's that lich, Corpse!
Corpse...
A warrior named Corpse. I like it.
You still not done?
I want to get my stats as high as I can
before the holy knights come after me...
Crowned Beast
Leading a double life isn't easy.
Fay.
Lady Roxy.
I have a secret mission for you, Fay.
Is it another inspection?
You should be able to see it now, Fay.
That land belongs to the Hart family.
Isn't it beautiful?
Then this secret mission...
Are we harvesting grapes?
Do you remember how grapes from our
vineyard were on sale at the market?
I wanted you to see them up close.
Welcome back, Roxy.
Mother!
I told you you didn't have to greet us.
It's all right. I'm feeling
better than usual today.
Please, don't overexert yourself.
Now, who might this be?
This is a servant that I hired.
I brought him to introduce to everyone.
Uh... It's nice to meet you.
I'm Fate Gra... Graphite.
I'm Aisha Hart. How nice of you to come.
You're welcome here, Fate.
Thank you so much.
That's a relief. She seems nice.
Yeah.
I'm wondering, Fate...
Yes?
Do you like my daughter?
M-Mother?!
Right out of the blue?!
Wh-Why would you ask him that, Mother?!
I'm just curious about his opinion
of you, as his employer.
That's what she meant... She scared me.
Then you should've said as much!
Madam Aisha.
I care a great deal for Lady Roxy.
And if I were allowed to,
I would like to serve her
until the end of my life.
Oh, my!
I-I'm going to rest for a bit in my room!
Did I say something wrong?
She always runs off whenever things
get uncomfortable. Hasn't changed at all.
Really?
Yes.
And when she was little,
she was quite the crybaby.
She'd throw a fit from
just a glimpse of a bug.
I'd never guess that from
how she acts in the capital.
I still have trouble believing my
little girl became a holy knight.
I worry she's pushing herself too hard.
After losing her father and suddenly
becoming head of the family...
Lady Roxy is a fine holy knight.
The people have a lot of faith in her,
and she performs her duties
as head of the house well.
I see.
Hold your sword here, and tuck your chin in.
Right.
I never thought you'd
become a holy knight...
Father, I want to be the kind
of holy knight that you are.
One who laughs along with the people!
I see.
As befits a member of the Hart family.
Right!
I still haven't fulfilled my promise...
Here. Freshly juiced.
Helps with fatigue.
Thank you.
It's delicious!
Ain't it, though?
The lords have personally helped
cultivate this land for generations.
Everyone on the property is proud to
have pitched in to create this flavor.
Even Sir Mason?
I hear he died in Galia.
It must be hard for Lady Roxy...
We weren't sure if she'd show up
this year. We're grateful she did.
Does Lady Roxy help with
the harvest every year?
That's part of it.
But she comes to hunt monsters, too.
Monsters?
This is harvest time for most
crops, not just grapes.
And that's when the monsters
show up looking for food.
What we're dealing with, kobolds,
come from that valley in the north.
Kobolds...
Well, you've been working hard!
Makes sense you'd be hungry.
After all those goblins, I'm not surprised.
Your Gluttony skill hungers
for some different souls.
Fay? Head on back without me, please.
I still have things to do.
Understood.
She's not from around here.
You there.
Her eyes... look just like mine!
Nothing's coming up?
Are you listening?
Oh, did you need something?
Looks like I'm too early.
Early for what?
Hey!
I came after those kobolds,
but you can have them.
You owe me one. We'll meet again.
Just who was that, Greed?
Couldn't tell you.
You know something, don't you?
What makes you think that?
You always pipe up without me asking,
but you're being awful quiet today.
Drop the attitude, would you?
There's some stuff even I,
in my greatness, don't know!
Why do you sound so proud of that?!
Could you take half of these, Fay?
Lady Roxy, when you said
you had something to do...
I went to get a share of the grapes.
She's... a Galian, I believe.
I thought Galia was destroyed.
That's what they say, yes.
Four thousand years ago, Galia
was a great military power...
But a surge in monsters caused their nation
to collapse, and most of their people died.
I guess there were survivors.
I don't think I've ever seen such
a full-blooded Galian before, either.
We should head back as well.
Lady Roxy... I heard about it.
This monster hunt...
Will you be okay on your own?
I won't be alone.
The warriors who work here will be with me.
And I am a holy knight, after all.
It won't be a problem!
Oh, this isn't good!
They got us!
Dammit... our grapes...
Those blasted beasts had a feast!
Those are kobolds?
This task is mine.
What is it?
There's something else over there...
What the hell is that?!
I've never seen one of that size before!
If your mouth's watering
at just the sight of it, then...
Time's running out.
I'm nearly in a starvation state...
I can't let Lady Roxy see me like that!
Before it comes to that...
Level 50?!
The Bringer of Lamentation
[Stats]
Vitality:
Strength:
Magic:
Spirit:
Agility:
[Skills]
Brawl
The Bringer of Lamentation, huh?
It's a crowned beast.
Crowned beast?
It's a powerful monster born from
accumulated aggression over a long time.
Nothing like the usual monsters.
This is bad news.
We don't stand a chance against that thing!
What do we do?
There's no need to worry. I will slay it.
I'm a holy knight.
And I will dedicate all of my power to
protecting this land and all of you.
Lady Roxy!
I ask for you workers to get to safety...
She can't manage this on her own.
Warriors, prepare for battle.
That thing's too much
for such a young holy knight.
If we're going to be
fully outfitted for battle,
we'll need until tomorrow to be ready.
That's fine. Please, do everything you can.
Right.
What now, Fate?
A monster at level 50 is too much
for me at the moment.
But... I can't ignore them...
And I can't ignore what's
happening in the Hart's lands.
Besides...
I will not let Lady Roxy die.
We're doing this, Greed!
Again with the hero act?
You must be really into it.
Shut up!
Those are kobold warriors
around the crowned beast.
The others are probably all kobold juniors.
You got any kinda plan, here?
I'm going to fight like a glutton.
Gluttony skill has activated.
[Stats]
Vitality:
Strength:
Magic:
Spirit:
Agility:
[Skills]
Gluttony,
Identify, Telepathy
Concealment,
One-Handed Sword
Technique,
Two-Handed Sword
Strength Boost (Low)
Strength Boost (Med)
Vitality Boost (Low)
Vitality Boost (Med)
Health Regen
Agility Boost (Med)
Still not enough.
Gluttony skill has activated.
Looks like this is over.
He caught them?!
We'll have to get in close and carve him up.
Right!
That's an art from the
Brawl skill, Ruinous Strike!
It can penetrate armor to
shatter bone and pulverize organs!
Watch out!
Snap out of it, Fate!
Pretending to be out cold?
That's a pretty slick trick you've learned.
Dammit!
Gluttony skill has activated.
You should be able to use
my first-level hidden art now!
I'll need 10% of your current stats!
We'll put a quick end to this!
Okay! Take it!
Fire away, Fate! Bloody Ptarmigan!
Looks like that health regen skill
you took from the goblin king
has already healed you up, too.
Hey, Greed...
What's up?
That was overkill!
You think so?
Gluttony skill has activated.
Wh-What is this... frenzy...?!
Aw, dammit.
You're overloaded from devouring
a soul of higher quality for the first time.
Fate, hold it in!
If you don't, it'll be even
worse than a starvation state!
Sword and arrow wounds...
Were these caused by magic arrows?
Who could've done this?
All that beautiful scenery
was torn to shreds...
Sorry about that, everyone!
Who could've done such a thing?
I saw a Galian girl the other day...
They're said to be even more
powerful than holy knights.
Maybe it was her?
But regardless, we can rest easy now.
Right.
Let's return to the capital.
When she's around Fate...
she makes the most wonderful face.
Fate, I have a favor to ask of you.
I'd like you to stay at my
daughter's side, to support her.
But... someone like me couldn't possibly...
I'm not asking you to
have prestige or authority...
Or strength, like a holy knight.
What makes you valuable is in here.
The desire to help her.
Heart...?
Yes. After all, that's how it was for me.
I was of common birth,
with no skill to speak of...
But I was still able to support my husband.
I believe having only a single holy knight
parent has caused Roxy some difficulty.
Madam Aisha!
I'm not long for this world.
Which is why... I want you
to be there for her...
Support Roxy, in my place.
Please.
I understand if you can't answer right away.
But... I ask you to consider it.
All right?
Right.
Am I worthy of something like that?
When I'm deceiving the world...
And carrying a secret like the Gluttony skill.
Why?!
I told you. Goblins won't cut it anymore.
But there are no stronger monsters
than goblins around here!
Time's running out, Fate. You need
to decide what comes next.
Really? That's remarkable.
I really don't have the right
to stand at Lady Roxy's side.
You hear the news? Sir Hado's going to
be joining the hunt for Corpse.
Hado?!
Probably his way of getting some
glory with an easy assignment.
They should send his ass to Galia,
where he can be monster food!
People like him always
stick to where it's safest.
Someone else is going to end up
on the Galia expedition.
An expedition to Galia?
Again? So soon after Sir Mason's death?
It's gonna be settled on soon.
I just hope the worst-case
scenario doesn't come true...
Father.
I've been assigned to
the expedition to Galia.
Please, watch over me.
Please, don't do this.
Fay?
Please don't go to Galia.
If you go now... you might not come back.
I've decided to go.
Lady Roxy...
The Hart family is a nuisance
for the Vlericks and other holy knights.
Rumor has it they arranged
for this expedition to Galia, too.
Dammit!
And now we'll finally be rid of that nuisance.
You can handle the rest, Hado.
And the two of you are off to
Tenbern, eh? Wish I was going, too.
This isn't just fun for us.
It's a research trip.
Isn't that right, Rafale?
Your research into "immortality," right?
I'm your little brother. Isn't it
about time you told me the truth?
How about it, brother?
I'm counting on you to
deal with this lich, Hado.
I can't overturn official orders.
And I can't stop Lady Roxy.
But...
I won't let them treat people
like trash and cause suffering!
You must be Corpse.
To Galia
"To Galia."